Ghost Recon: Alpha is a action, science fiction,
thriller film directed by François Alaux.
Ghost Recon: Alpha sees a team led by Ghost Leader infiltrate a trade at a
Russian depot between a general and a mysterious other figure.
The Boss, played by Charlotte Rampling.
Ghost Leader, played by Mark Ivanir.
30K, played by Keith Gilmore.
MP, played by Pavel Ledinsky.
Sokolov, played by Erich Redman.
Pepper, played by Joplin Sibtain.
Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon is a series of military tactical
shooter video games published by Ubisoft.
In the series, the player is in charge of a
fictional, newly conceived squad of U.S.
Army Special Forces soldiers from Delta Company, 1st Battalion, 5th
Special Forces Group (5th SFG) stationed at Fort Bragg.
Except for the "1st Battalion, 5th SFG" designation, this reconnaissance unit is entirely fictional,
as Special Forces Battalions currently only support three Companies (A, B and C).
They are often referred to as "the Ghosts".
Their role is like other real world special operations forces, in
that their operations are kept highly classified.
In Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon: Future Soldier, it is shown that the Ghost's unit has multiple designations and is part of JSOC; they are also known as the Group for
Specialized Tactics (or GST—where the term "Ghost" comes from), much like real JSOC units such as Delta Force (1st SFOD-D or CAG) and SEAL Team Six (or DEVGRU).
Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon has also been novelized by Grant
Blackwood under the pseudonym David Michaels.
As of 2025, over 40 million units have been sold.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.